let MCQS = [{
    question: "Who Played Chris Gardner in the movie 'The Pursuit of Happyness'?",
    choice1: "Chris Evans",
    choice2: "Samuel L. Jackson",
    choice3: "Will Smith",
    choice4: "Tom Hanks",
    answer: 2
},
            {
            question: "Which is the No. 01 collection movie in world?",
    choice1: "Avatar",
    choice2: "Avengers: Endgame",
    choice3: "Avatar: The Way of Water",
    choice4: "Titanic",
    answer: 0
},
            {
            question: "Who is main villen in the movie 'Spiderman: No Way Home'?",
    choice1: "Electro",
    choice2: "Green Goblin",
    choice3: "Venom",
    choice4: "Doctor Octopus",
    answer: 1
},
            {
            question: "What is kill count of John Wick in the movie 'John Wick: Chapter 3'?",
    choice1: "108",
    choice2: "67",
    choice3: "147",
    choice4: "94",
    answer: 3
},
            {
            question: "How many Oscars Nominations did the 1997 movie 'Titanic' got?",
    choice1: "13",
    choice2: "9",
    choice3: "10",
    choice4: "14",
    answer: 3
},
            {
            question: "In which form did 'The Jungle Book' originally appear?In which form did 'The Jungle Book' originally appear?",
    choice1: "Radio Play",
    choice2: "Film",
    choice3: "Book",
    choice4: "An app",
    answer: 2
},
            {
               question: "What is name of Emma Stone's character in movie 'La La Land'?",
    choice1: "Mia Dolan",
    choice2: "Gwen Stacy",
    choice3: "Wichita",
    choice4: "Hannah Clark",
    answer: 0
},{
               question: "Who is the most oldest superhero in the comics?",
    choice1: "Superman",
    choice2: "The Phantom",
    choice3: "Mrs. Marvel",
    choice4: "Batman",
    answer: 1
},
            {
               question: "Who is the director of movie 'Dangal'?",
    choice1: "Karan Johar",
    choice2: "Zoya Akhtar",
    choice3: "Nitish Tiwari",
    choice4: "S. S. Rajamouli",
    answer: 2
},
            {
               question: "What was the first movie based on a book?",
    choice1: "The Godfather",
    choice2: "The Wolf of Wall Street",
    choice3: "Forrest Gump",
    choice4: "Cinderella",
    answer: 3
}];